[CLEARS THROAT LOUDLY]
Why didn't you just have soup at home?
(Sheldon:)Penny, I have an IQ of 187.
(Sheldon:)Don't you imagine
that if there were a way for me...
(Sheldon:)...to have had soup at home,
I would have thought of it?
(Penny:)You can have soup delivered.
(Sheldon:)I did not think of that.
(Sheldon:)Clearly, febrile delirium is setting in.
(Sheldon:)Please bring me some soup
while I still understand what a spoon is for.
Okay. What kind of soup do you want?
(Sheldon:)Well, my mother used to make me
this split-pea...
(Sheldon:)...with little frankfurter slices
and these homemade croutons.
(Penny:)We have chicken, tortilla and potato leek.
(Sheldon:)Can I get any of those with little
frankfurter slices and homemade croutons?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)Then surprise me.
[BLOWS NOSE]